teamtechnology.co.uk 2015-06-09

# Cookie Information

This page lists the cookies we have stored on your computer and details our privacy policy.

## Cookies

Cookies are private pieces of information that are needed for us to run our website. Some information is unique to you and helps us provide you with a service, for example when you complete a personality questionnaire. Some cookies contain anonymous information and help us improve the overall service to all our visitors, for example Google Analytics tells us which pages are unpopular.

We use cookies. If you do not wish to accept cookies in your browser, please delete them and leave the website. For information on whether or how we use your information, please see our [Privacy Policy](http://www.teamtechnology.co.uk/privacy.html)

> > ## Privacy Policy

### Overview

Any information you provide is used only to operate this website and provide you with information and/or services that you ask for. We do not use your information for marketing purposes, nor pass it to anyone else for marketing. How we collect and use your information is detailed below. In summary, the main points are:

  * The only time we pass your information to anyone else is if you purchase a report or install the Facebook App. If you purchase a report, we pass your details automatically to Paypal so they can process your payment, and they pass details of your transaction back to us. If you use the Facebook App, some of your personality questionnaire results are shared with your friends.
  * As with most websites, our system keeps logs to record how the website is used. These logs are anonymous, except for log entries related to report purchases.
  * There are a small number of other cases, detailed below, where we may need to pass your data to someone else for technical/legal reasons (e.g., if we sell the business).

### Detail

This is the privacy policy that is in operation at www.teamtechnology.co.uk. It sets out how we use your information. If you have any questions about this privacy policy please contact us using the menus at the top of the page. By using the website and giving your information to us you are deemed to have accepted the terms of this privacy policy.

### Information we Collect About You

The website automatically collects certain information, including: the site and/or page you visited previously; the browser you are using; and your IP address. This information does not identify you. We use it for internal purposes to monitor how the website is being used.

If you complete an online personality questionnaire on the website, your results are stored in a cookie on your computer and on our database. The information is used either (a) so we can retrieve your results if you contact us or (b) as anonymous information for research purposes only.

If you purchase a report or otherwise contact us with an email address, we do not use it for marketing purposes or pass your information on to anyone else. We will only contact you when it is necessary as part of the service we provide, or if you have chosen to opt-in to a mailing list.

### Who we Share Your Information With

We do not share your information with anyone except:

  * we may pass your information to the police or another similar body if it is requested
  * if we sell Team Technology or merge with another business we may pass your information to the prospective purchaser or the other business.
  * If you ask us for information about a consultancy service we may give your email address to one of our associates so they can reply to you.
  * If you purchase a report, we pass your order information to Paypal so they can process your order.
  * If you install the Facebook App, your personality type and individual profile is used to provide reports to those of your Facebook friends who have also installed the App.

### Security

We do our best to keep your information secure. The website has security features such as backups and firewalls etc. If you purchase a report, the password to the report is embedded in the link we send you. Please contact us if you wish the link to be disabled after you have downloaded your reports.

### Links to Other Sites

There are links to other websites on teamtechnology.co.uk - e.g., to Paypal for the secure processing of your report order. These sites have their own privacy policies and we are not liable for any use made of your information by such websites.

### Cookies

We use cookies to hold some of your information - a cookie is a piece of information stored in your browser. This includes your questionnaire results, and you can delete the cookies on the "Delete Cookie" page of your online reports.

You may set your internet browser to reject cookies. However, if you do so you may not be able to use all of the functions of the website - e.g., you will not be able to transfer your questionnaire results into the Facebook App.

Google, as a third party vendor, also uses cookies so they can serve appropriate ads to you based on your visits to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of Google's cookie system at their website, for example see: <http://www.google.co.uk/policies/privacy/>. We also use Google Analytics to provide anonymous information about how our website is used.

### General

English Law applies to this privacy policy.  Any dispute will be heard by the English courts. You are deemed to have accepted this when you use the website.
